# Taha Huda

#### Profile

Action-oriented individual with good knowledge in Finance, Research, Operations, management and Data Analysis. Data-driven decision making abilities with statistics, probability, critical thinking. Equipped with proficient social skills yet more effectively unescorted. More than 4 years of experience working with Ms-Excel, Google Sheet and SQL.

# Professional Courses

## **Google Data Analytics Certification**

Oct, 2021 - Mar 2022

## JP Morgan Investment Banking Virtual Experience

Mar, 2022 - May, 2022

## Reading Professional Financial statement at CFI

Dec, 2020 - Feb, 2021

#### Excel Crash Course-Spreadsheet formulas for finance at CFI

Jan, 2021 - Feb, 2021

# Corporate Finance at University of Pennsylvania

May 2024 - May 2024

# Work History

#### Head of Opeartion's from Enigma Gaming Pvt Ltd

Jan 2023 - May 2024

Developing and implementing long-term and short-term operational strategies aligned with the organization's goals and objectives. Leading and managing teams across various operational functions such as event management, player relations, broadcast production, and venue operations. Establishing and overseeing operating budgets, which include distributing funds wisely to support important projects while preserving financial viability.

# Data Research Intern(Business and Personal Finance) from Vertigo Studio SA(Romania)

Aug 2022- Oct 2022

Working with larger dataset organizing, sorting, filtering the data Researching business and finance related data from first party sources i.e, USA governmental portals or different research websites.

Creating effective visualization with data also framing effective questions to make the research more appropriate.

Monitored the Global and Indian Financial markets to make informed decisions.

## Market research Intern from Wattmonk Technologies Pvt Ltd

May 2022 - July 2022

Utilized diverse research techniques and online or published data collection tools to amass key information or statistics, supporting business objectives. Devised questionnaires, surveys and open forum discussions to generate real-time data collection from target demographic. Completed research, compiled data and assisted in timely reporting.

#### Financial Analyst Intern from Munify

#### **Details**

tahahudawrk@gmail.com

8898641091

DOB -: 30/06/2001-India, Thane - 401 107

#### Links

**LinkedIn** 

#### **Skills**

Management

Research

Ms-Excel

**Data Analytics** 

SQL

Communication

Visualizations

#### Languages

Hindi

English

#### **Hobbies**

**Reading Books** 

Fitness & Nutrition

Jan 2023-Apr2023

Creating the national municipal financial database by preparing and reviewing data sets in MS-Excel, Formatting such datasets for upload in the database and normalization of State Codes as per national codes(national Municipal Accounts Manual) Worked on texting and analyzing the database output involving the budget, accounts, and financial ratios of municipalities.

## Sales Associate from Mos Designs

Mar 2021 - April 2022

Assists clients in making product selections. stimulates sales via sharing product expertise, engaging consumers, and suggestive selling. extends a warm greeting to and welcomes guests. answers the inquiries of clients.

### Education

# Bachelor's of Accounting and Finance at Shree LR Tiwari Degree College, Mumbai

Feb, 2019 - May, 2022

# Commerce stream at Thakur College of Science and Commerce

Jun, 2017 - Feb, 2019

# **≜** Academic Research / Project Work

May 2024 - May 2024

**RESEARCH WORK 1:** 

Analysis of financial markets (Final year research)

Technologies used: google Docs, Excel, Statistical tools (anova,

coorelation).

Associated: Bachelors in Accounting and Finance (Shree Lr Tiwari Degree college)

Aims and objective of research:

- To analyze relationship between awareness of analysis of financial markets and knowledge of analysis .
- To study relationship between investment and profitability
- Conducted a descriptive research with sample size of 97 to back our thesis.

PROJECT WORK 1: Cost Benefit Analysis: customer Relationship

Management (CRM)

Platform Technologies: google sheets Associated : Coursera Project network

Description:

- customer Relationship Management (CRM) Platform
- Considering tangible and intangible costs & benefit.
- Breakeven point & ROI

PROJECT WORK 2: Investment risk management

Associated: Coursera project Network

Technologies used: google finance, google sheets

Description:

- monthly returns and standard deviation
- calculation 1. Beta, 2. Treynor ratio 3. VAR(value at risk) 95%,99% for companies Facebook, Amazon, Apple, Netflix, Google. By using SPX (s&p 500) as a benchmark.